kooding.com 2018-02-01

# Korean Fashion Online Shopping | American Fashion Clothing

We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy carefully.  
This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting the Site directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.

**OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS**

KOODING.com collects customer data, which is provided voluntarily in an effort to improve and enhance our customer's online shopping experience and for marketing and promotional use only. Customers are only added to our e-mail and mailing list if they opt to register or enter a contest. Customers have the option to be removed from the list at any time, correct or update your personal information, and disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account.

You can make these requests at the customer information section of the Site [https://www.Kooding.com/help.php?section=contactus](https://www.kooding.com/help.php?section=contactus), or emailing your request to customer service:  

**USE OF COOKIES AND PIXEL TAGS**

(a) Cookies and Other Technology. Like many sites, the Site employs cookies and web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation of the Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your Site usage.

(b) Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of the Site. We have to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase.

(c) Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on the Site has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any electronic image on the Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a web beacon. (d) We may use third-party advertising companies to help tailor site content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which web pages are visited or what products are purchased and in what amount). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us.

(e) Log Files. As is true of most web sites, the Site server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access the Site. We may also log your Internet protocol ("IP") address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address may indicate the location of your computer on the Internet.)

(f) Product Reviews. You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we will ask for your email address and geographic location. If you submit a review, your geographic location will be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private). Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information.

(g)Google Remarketing Analytics.

  * KOODING.com implements and use Display Advertising.
  * The Google Analytics features KOODING.com has implemented is based on Displayed Advertising.
  * Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCg4VHd0m21adYaAg9yNDxJFQTiTSdorWliAwloVbVUTgmchctwp2GJgAjNVdX5eTnvU_liK7Nw1FGvAO2MinLUps2ts4sc__SSyVF7FCU6gglVus727677iacDuZaJDGl9s2vkWKy9gmbFnJTyVHgeNeMVjqG3WCh_5C10Gqr73KbdwD0__6mf5ax3UV_6tHffg9HzX).

Here is the link to the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

  * KOODING.com uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.
  * Third-party vendors, including Google, show KOODING.com ads on sites across the Internet.
  * KOODING.com and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to KOODING.com.

**SECURE SHOPPING**

KOODING.com uses industry standard security measures called SSL (secure socket layer encryption). SSL encrypts sensitive information like credit card numbers before they are sent over the Internet. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. We believe that their security procedures are adequate. For example, when you visit the Site, you access servers that are kept in a secure physical environment, behind a locked cage and an electronic firewall.

**COPYRIGHT**

All materials, including images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips and written and other materials that are part of this site are copyrights, trade address, and/or other intellectual property owned, controlled or licensed by KOODING.com and its contracted vendors.

**UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at [CustomerService@Kooding.com](mailto:customerservice@kooding.com).
